<resources>
    <!-- Main (Start) Activity -->
    <string name="app_name">up887818</string>
    <string name="title">My First Week at a Fast Food Restaurant</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Intro">Type in your name to get started!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_introduction">Introduction</string>

    <!-- Introduction Activity -->
    <string-array name="intro_explaination">
        <item>Hi %s! I\'m Scott and I am your supervisor here at Fast Food.</item>
        <item>You start work on Monday and have a week probationary period.</item>
        <item>Each day you will take responsibility for the hygiene of the restaurant as well as serve customers.</item>
        <item>If you mess up, you may have to go back to your previous work... or worse, you could get fired!</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Hygiene Activities -->
    <!-- Activity 0: Cleaning the kitchen -->
    <string-array name="hygieneactivity0">
        <item>Scott has asked you to clean the kitchen floor. Will you do it?</item>
        <item>You have cleaned the floor, but it is now wet. Do you bother drying the floor?</item>
        <item>Someone slipped and hurt themselves on the wet floor! You are a liability for our restaurant.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Activity 1: Dropped burger -->
    <string-array name="hygieneactivity1">
        <item>Whilst cooking, you dropped a raw burger onto the floor. Do you pick it up?</item>
        <item>Do you bin the burger or cook it?</item>
        <item>The burger was contaminated from touching the floor and made someone sick! You are a liability for our restaurant.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Activity 2: Cleaning the toilets -->
    <string-array name="hygieneactivity2">
        <item>It is your turn to clean the toilets. Do you refill the soap?</item>
        <item>Now that there\'s soap, do you clean the toilets?</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Activity 3: Emptying the bins -->
    <string-array name="hygieneactivity3">
        <item>The bins are getting full. Do you empty them?</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Activity 4: ?? -->
    <string-array name="hygieneactivity4"></string-array>
    <!--Todo: create hygiene activity 4 -->

    <!-- Customer Service Activities -->
    <!-- Activity 0: Unintelligible customer -->
    <string-array name="customeractivity0">
        <item>You are running the drive thru and the customer is difficult to hear. Do you ask them to repeat themselves?</item>
        <item>You misheard the customer and now the order is wrong. Are you going to fix it?</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Activity 1: Large order -->
    <string-array name="customeractivity1">
        <item>A large order comes in the drive thru. Are you going to ask them to park up and wait?</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Activity 2: Ketchup Packets -->
    <string-array name="customeractivity2">
        <item>A customer asks for extra ketchup when it usually costs money. Do you give it to them for free?</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Activity 3: Declined Payment -->
    <string-array name="customeractivity3">
        <item>The customer\'s card gets declined. Do you let them try again?</item>
        <item>It declines for a second time. Do you give them free food out of pity?</item>
        <item>You did not ask for the manager\'s permission before giving the free food.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Activity 4: ?? -->
    <string-array name="customeractivity4"></string-array>
    <!-- Todo: create customer activities 4 -->

    <!-- Todo: update lucidchart with new activities -->
</resources>
